13691530067 jackieyang51@gmail.com www.yangjunrui.com

Profile

Born with great talent, I'm admitted to gifted and talented class in Beijing No.8 Middle School, and then enrolled in Peking University in my 16. I have great learning ability, I have experience in interdisciplinary research. I'm also able to organise a development project. A project founded by me, "Pocket Printer", won many awards.

I take part in many software hardware co-design project. I have done research at both computer science and bio-engineering lab, giving me insight on automation and cutting edge research in life science.

Education

2006.09-2009.06 Gifted and Talented Class of Beijing No.8 Middle School

2009.09-2012.06 High School affiliated to Renmin University

2012.09-2016.06 (Expected) Peking University

Ability

Fluent English skills (TOFEL: 107)

Programming in C/C++, use script language scheme, python and javascript

.Net Framework, WinForm and C#

iOS, OSX Application with Objective-C

Experienced in micro controller programming (ATMega and Cortex-M platform)

Experience

INTERN, HUANG LAB, BIODYNAMIC OPTICAL IMAGING CENTER, PEKING UNIVERSITY - 2013.6-PRESENT 2013.06-2013.12 Build "Cell Picker", a Computer assisted high throughput single cell acquiring system

Built the whole software system and part of the hardware structure.

Introduced our project to Chairman Xi when he visited Peking University.

2014.05-2014.06 Build a bioinformatics program to analyse DNA Barcoding sequencing result

Implement the program.

2014.06-2014.07 Build a automated droplet generating system

Build all the software and hardware system.

INTERN, RECONFIGURABLE ARCHITECTURE FOR WIRELESS TEAM, CENTER FOR ENERGY-EFFECIENT COMPUTING AND APPLICATIONS, PEKING UNIVERSITY - 2014.2-PRESENT

2014.07-2014.08 help build the linux driver for our software defined radio system

Port this system to a more commonly used driver ath9k.

Projects

2013.09-2014.09 "Pocket Printer"

Pocket printer is a printer that can fit in a pocket. To achieve this, I cancelled the paper feeding system in traditional printer, and placed a navigating system formed by several mouse navigating sensor. I expected the printer can print the pattern depending on the relative location of the printer.

Hardware and software co-design. Lead the development group. Designed the circuit board, the software logic inside the microcontroller, and the client software in phone.

Awards

- 2011 National Olympiad in Informatics in Provinces, Second Prize
- 2012 Peking University ACM/ICPC, Third Prize
- 2013 International Youth Innovation Competition, Golden Prize
- 2013 Peking University Industrial Engineering Competition, First Prize
- 2013 "Challenge Cup" National College Student Curricular Academic Science and Technology Works Competition, Second Prize in Peking University
- 2013 Peking University Prize for social/community work
- 2013 Honorable Mention in Mathematical Contest in Modelling
- 2013 Peking University ACM/ICPC, Third Prize
- 2014 Peking University Innovation Prize
- 2014 Peking University Founder Prize